<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase">
    <modNameReadable>SimplyMoreBridges</modNameReadable>
    <linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2012484790</linkUrl>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>SimplyMoreBridges_1_0_11_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0.11.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>Did a bit of a rewrite of the mod and it is now possible to build bridges of all stoney and metaly materials. This includes materials added by other mods.
This option can be enabled in the settings if desired and requires a restart of the game to have effect. The cost of the bridges are the same for all materials, except for high value materials like gold or silver.

I also have an idea for making bridgable versions of all loaded floors that actually counts as floors. If this is something that you would like to see, please leave a comment on the mod page as it will require some more coding and I try to only do changes/additions that are wanted.
</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>SimplyMoreBridges_1_0_17_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0.17.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>A small addition to the mod. There is now an option to generate more styles of tiles for the bridges. The original uses the stone tiles for the stony bridges and the normal tile for the metal-bridges.
With the option turned on there will also be a flagstone-style for each stone-bridge and a paved tile-style for each metal bridge. There will also be a concrete-style for the steel bridge.
Hope this will be of use to someone!
</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>SimplyMoreBridges_1_0_19_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0.19.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>Small update, added a sterile bridge by request. It can be activated in the options if you turn on the generation of bridges from more materials. I may add more floorlike bridges if there is an interest of it, please leave a comment if this is something you would like to see.
</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>SimplyMoreBridges_1_3_2</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.3.2</assemblyVersion>
    <content>If you enable the option "Generate bridges from more materials" the mod will now also generate bridges from all woody-materials if any are loaded. 
So for example Bamboo and Iron Wood from VGP or Bones from the Bones-mod could be used to build wooden bridges instead of just the vanilla WoodLog.</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>